<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Final Project</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Final Project</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 15 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Python post</title>
      <link>/blog/python-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/python-post/</guid>
      <description>Python is one of the most popular programming languages in the world, and it is getting progressively more popular every day! Python is great for lots of things, but in this example I will show how it can be used in the realm of biology for the purpose of aligning sequences of DNA. The Needlman-Wunsch algorithim was developed in 1970 for the purpose of finding the optimal alignment of two different DNA sequences.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Oct 2016 22:55:05 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/</guid>
      <description>Projects Here are some projects I have been working on:
  Project 1
  Project 2
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/test_resume/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/test_resume/</guid>
      <description>JAKSON JOHNSONJaksonjohnson99@gmail.comAustin, TX 78705 • (832)-878-3651
EDUCATION
The University of Texas at Austin Bachelor of Biology May 2020Minor: Business FoundationsOverall GPA: 3.78
Oak Ridge High School Unweighted GPA: 3.97Weighted Class Rank: 9 of 917 May 2017
EXPERIENCE
Schoolhouse Pediatrics – Medical Assistant; Austin, TX July 2018 – Present• Prepare patients for evaluation by a physician by updating their medical records and histories• Obtain vital measurements (blood pressure, pulse, height, weight, etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project 1</title>
      <link>/project1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project1/</guid>
      <description>Intro: The datasets I have chosen to work with are “drug_use_table” and “CrimeStatebyState_2_”. The “drug_use_table” dataset is sourced from Center for Behavioral Health Statistics and Quality and Substance Abuse and Mental Health Services Administration, both of which collected data from every state regarding self-reported drug use from 2004-2014. This data was then complied into one comprehensive dataset. The “drug_use_table” contains 31 variables, 28 of which represent the number of people who self-reported the use of specific drug.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project 2: Modeling, Testing, and Predicting</title>
      <link>/project2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project2/</guid>
      <description>The plantTraits dataset contains various morphological and reproductive measurements of 136 different plant species(the plantTraits2 dataset used contains only the complete cases from the orginal dataset and therefore only contains 78 different species). Considering that there are 31 total variables, I will only introduce the ones used in this analysis. The “pdias” variable is a numeric variable which contains the diaspore(seed body) mass(mg) for each species. The “longindex” numeric variable is a measure of how long each species’ seed can live in a seed bank with values ranging from 0 to 1 (these values are relative to each other and do not represent a certain measure of time).</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>